Ibrahima Barry

Ibrahima Barry is a recent graduate of the University of Essex, from where he earned his degree in Electronic Engineering. He is a fast learner and appreciates the importance of flexibility and adaptability towards achieving his goals. As an example, during the period of writing his thesis, Ibrahima learned how to operate a humanoid robot using specialized software within a couple of weeks. He also participated in team exercises requiring the programming of robots to do certain tasks. Consequently, Ibrahima sees himself as a team player with robust organizational skills and capability to organize tasks effectively.

Work History

2023-01 - Electronics Intern

2023-03 Assute

Assutech

- Learned how to use Arduino software and hardware
- Completed introductory courses in Python and C++.

2022-05 - University of Essex

• Numbers Regular Project, holding afterschool sessions to

help children with math.

2016-06 - Web Development Intern

2016-08 Assutech – Banjul

• Learned how to design websites with HTML and CSS.

Education

2019-10 - BEng: Electronic Engineering

2023-05
University of Essex - Colchester, United Kingdom

2017-09 - A levels

2019-05 Finborough School - Stowmarket, United Kingdom

Physics, Computer Science, and Math

Certifications

| 2023-03 | Public Speaking, Forbes Academy, Banjul |
|---------|---|
| 2022-11 | Interpersonal Communications, Montgomery College, Online |
| 2018-11 | IDEA Duke of York Silver Award, Finborough School, Online |

Contact

Address

Boyds, MD, 20841

Phone

301-755-8087

E-mail

iab.jr10@gmail.com

Skills

Problem Solving

Adaptability

Public Speaking

Teamwork

Communication